



bajram.ramadan@hotmail.com



www.bajramramadan.com

BAJRAM RAMADAN

CREATIVE DESIGNER & DEVELOPER



ABOUT ME

My name is Bajram, I'm Creative Designer & Developer from Macedonia. Outside of my full-time commitments, I love being outdoors, exploring nature. Nature gives me the power to create amazing user experiences which make customers and users satisfied when they're using products.

I've been a Creative Designer & Developer for the last 5 years, currently working full-time as a freelancer.

My expertise depends on website optimization, I deliver high quality and optimized code.

WORK **EXPERIENCE**

CREATIVE DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

2018 — Present

FREELANCER

Creating websites and applications across multiple browsers for desktop, tablet and smartphones with top technologies.

- Implementing a mobile-first approach to existing websites, and optimizing them.
- Working directly with client stakeholders to develop technical solutions for business.

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

2015 — 2018

3PIX MEDIA

Developing news portal with API for future to communicate with mobile apps. Creating simple E-Commerce WordPress website with Woo Commerce plugin.

- Creating new features, functionality and capabilities on the E-Commerce and News portals using WordPress API, Node.js and MySQL.
- Development of software solutions using latest Open Source technologies in both, front-end and back-end development.

INTERNSHIP

Jan 2014 - March 2014

MASSIVE CLOUDS

Developing simple dashboard application that will help the company to manage the clients.

- Learning Ruby programming language and meet with Rails framework for developing web applications.
- Rails Front-End Prototyping and Design.



+389 78 297 741



bajram.ramadan@hotmail.com



www.bajramramadan.com

BAJRAM RAMADAN

CREATIVE DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

JAVASCRIPT I & JAVASCRIPT II

2018 — 2019

SEMOS EDUCATION

 Basic understanding about Node.js and React.js, Good understanding of server side-templates, basic of Mongo DB (Create, Read, Update, Delete).

Basic knowledge of the life cycle of a web application, basic knowledge of the constituent elements of web application, ability to create custom modules, basic building blocks of one Node.js application, convenient knowledge for connecting and inserting data in MongoDB, application of FS and HTTP modules and Expression Express as constituents of a modern application in Node.js.

PROFESSIONAL WEB DEVELOPER & CLOUD ENGINEER FOR ENTERPRISE

2012 - 2013

SEDC CODE ACADEMY

 1-year Academy for programming where you learn from ground to cloud technologies such as HTM LS, CSS3, JS, jQuery and Latest Microsoft Technologies Asp net MVC, SQL DB, C#, Azure Cloud Computing.

This curriculum is focused on the latest web technologies combined with traditional computer science concepts. Having in mind that a great web developer means not only being fluent with the latest frameworks and programming languages, but also having an evolved intuition for writing code that is efficient, secure and maintainable, the study methodology has an ideal balance between these crucial components.

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

DESIGN SKILLS

- UI/UX Design
- Web Design
- Photoshop
- Illustrator

CODING SKILLS

- HTML5 / CSS3
- jQuery/JavaScript
- WordPress
- Node.JS / React.js

AWARDS

THREE MUSKETEERS

2013 / CODEFEST

Best app developed by three people.

NASA SPACE APPS CHALLENGE

2013 / NASA

For participating in the first NASA Space App Challenge in the Republic of Macedonia.

REFERENCES

SALI MEMED

CEO | 3PIX MEDIA

P: +389 78 441 429

E:salimemed@yahoo.com

MUSTAFA JAKUPOV

DIRECTOR / RROMA

P: +389 76 548 181

E: mustafa@rromassn.org

+389 78 297 741

bajram.ramadan@hotmail.com

www.bajramramadan.com

BAJRAM RAMADAN

CREATIVE DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

CERTIFICATES

